floridahostweb.com 2009-09-14

# Florida Host Web | Privacy Policy

Florida Host Web, Inc. is a private non-profit company. Our Web site guests and customers privacy is our top priority. Florida Host Web will never sell, distribute, or trade any personal information gathered on the domain floridahostweb.com. 

#### Intro

To be able to provide you with services you are applying for, sometimes we need to collect your personal data. This can happen when you register at our support forums or when buying or downloading our products. Beside this, we collect some non personal information for the purposes of observation. The privacy policy explains when we need to take such information, what kind of information it is, how it is used, security of your information and third party issues. When and what information is collected. 

When a user downloads our products (regardless of type, platform, price or if it is free), Florida Host Web tracks and logs IP addresses of visitors to Florida Host Web. This information is securely stored in the Florida Host Web database and is used to protect floridahostweb.com and its customers from hacker and spamming attempts. Much like any other collected private information, IP addresses will not be sold, distributed or traded with any third parties. Furthermore, IP address information will never be used in conjunction with marketing of any kind. 

Florida Host Web may use cookies to store information on your local computer. These cookies do not contain any of the information you have entered while registering or making payments; they serve only to improve your viewing pleasure. The e-mail address is used only for confirming your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one). 

#### Use of information

Florida Host Web obliges itself to use all the information collected from visitors and members solely to be able to provide specific services or products, inform on events happening related to Florida Host Web, or in statistics purposes. No commercial use, selling or giving to any third party, is permitted. 

#### Security

Florida Host Web commits to apply maximum security efforts to guard the security of information provided by guests and customers. Florida Host Web takes no responsibility of such information becoming available to the third party in the result of unauthorized access or such taking place beyond our control. Nevertheless the visitors shall understand that by posting personal information on forums and providing it publicly they do it at their own risk. Florida Host Web holds no responsibility for misuse of such private information by other users of forums. If you post personal information in a public place such as a forum, this information becomes public. Therefore it is advised not to post any personal information on any public forums or blogs related to Florida Host Web. 

#### Third party

Florida Host Web will not pass along any private information collected on floridahostweb.com to any third parties without prior express consent from the related user or customer. 

#### Google Advertising Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

#### Amendments

Florida Host Web, Inc. retains the right to amend any part of this privacy policy and include necessary additions at any time without warning. While it is our policy to notify registered users of Florida Host Web of any changes to our Privacy Policy, it is the responsibility of the end-user to review the Privacy Policy on a monthly basis for changes and updates. 

#### Contacting Us

Should you have any questions or inquiries concerning the floridahostweb.com privacy policy, the treatment of information you provide, or your business with Florida Host Web, Inc., feel free to send them to [customerservice@floridahostweb.com](mailto:customerservice@floridahostweb.com)

#### Payment Processing

All payment processing is executed securely by PayPal (www.paypal.com). Florida Host Web does not receive, save, store nor transmit any customer payment information including but not limited to: Credit Card Numbers, Check Numbers, Account Numbers, Bank Numbers, Bank Names, Debit Card Information, or any other private financial records. All financial transactions are executed exclusively by PayPal, therefore all payment disputes, payment inquiries, payments statements and other information related to online payments must be made towards PayPal. NEVER POST OR SEND PERSONAL FINANCIAL INFORMATION ANYWHERE WHILE ON THE DOMAIN, FLORIDAHOSTWEB.COM. The address bar must list the domain as paypal.com for it to be a valid, secure transaction. Florida Host Web is not responsible for the security of any financial information that is posted or sent while under the floridahostweb.com domain. 

#### Terms of Use Policy

Violation of any outlined Privacy Policy rules and explanations is a direct violation of the Terms of Use Policy. Please review the Terms of Use Policy for further details. Violators of the Terms of Use Policy may be 1)Suspended from use of floridahostweb.com, 2)Blocked from visiting floridahostweb.com, 3)Reported to the appropriate authorities. Violating the Terms of Use Policy nullifies any privacy protection floridahostweb.com offers. Upon such violation any and/or all information collected by such user can and/or will be used to block IP addresses, block user access, block domain access and/or sent to third parties whom participate in fighting spammers and hackers globally. Violators private information can and/or will be forwarded to the appropriate authorities. 

|
